A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4 FA1402
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Training Programs, 1971-2005; 4
  - Taipei Fellows, 1993-2003; 9
    - Taipei, Declinations - Ho, Wu-Chang, Arts Administration 2, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Chu, Huey-fen, Arts Administration 3, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Kao Chynan-Wann, Simon, Art Administration 4, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Li-Min, Kuo, Art Administration 5, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Chin-Yu, Yuan, Art Administration 6, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Mu-Shan, Chen, Art Administration 7, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Shun-Chu, Chen, Art Organization 2, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Li-Shai, Lee, Movie 3, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Shou-Yuo, Liu, Theatre 1, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - An-Chi, Liu, Art Creation 1, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Hui-fen, Deng, Art Creation 4, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Hsing-Yu, Chang, Art Creation 5, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Tzu-Chih, Huang, Art Creation 6, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Yung, Liu, Art Creation 7, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Kuo-King, Tung, Art Creation 8, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations - Sheng-An, Yang, Art Creation 9, 2000 Spring (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 2001 Spring (Box 398, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 2002 Spring (Box 398, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, Declinations, 2003 Spring (Box 399, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 2000 (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 1999 (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 1998 (Box 400, Folder 4)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 400, Folder 5)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - Taipei, General Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program, 1991-1992; 10
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Pan, Li-Chun, 1991 (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Yu, Shiu-Chin, 1991 (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Liang, Jui-Jung, 1991 (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Lin, Shu-Hui, 1991 (Box 402, Folder 5)
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Hsu, Tzyy-yann, 1992 (Box 402, Folder 6)
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Shih, Chen, 1992 (Box 402, Folder 7)
    - Taiwan Dance Fellowship Program - Tseng, Chiung-wei, 1992 (Box 402, Folder 8)
  - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program, 1993-1995; 11
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Liang, Chi-ming, 1993 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Shih, Yung, 1993 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Huang, Ya-lin, 1994 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Lee, Yung-feng, 1994 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Wang, Yo-huei, 100-0-4110-203.000-3 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Huang, Teresa L. C., 1994 (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Li, Nien-Lou, 1995 (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Hsu, Jui-Fang, 1995 (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Ma, Pao-Shan, 1995 (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Arts Fellowship Program - Chen, Hsing-Wan, 1995 (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan Fellowship Program, 1996-2005; 12
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Chen, Wen Chyou-Chu, 1996 (Box 410, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Liu, Jui-Chi (Box 410, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Wu, I-Fang, 1996 (Box 410, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Huang, Hsu-hui, 1997 (Box 410, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Shen, Hsiu-Yen, 1997 (Box 410, Folder 5)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Hsu, Wen-Chin, 1997 (Box 410, Folder 6)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Wu, Wen-Tsui, 1998 (Box 411, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program, SAACF - Taipei Dance Workshop (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Liu, Shih-Tung, 1998 (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Wang, Rong-yu, 1998 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Tao, Ya-Lun, 1998 (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Huang, Susan Shih-shan, 1998 (Box 412, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Kuo, Chun-Ming, Bula, 1998 (Box 412, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Chen, Yi-Wen, 1999 (Box 412, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Tsai, Huey-Yuan, 1999 (Box 412, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Peng, Shih-Sheng, 1999 (Box 413, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship Program - Cho, Ting-Chu, 1999 (Box 413, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Chiang - Fu-Chin, 2002 (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Lee, Jin-Yang (Jiun-Yang Li), 2002 (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Hung. Tung-Lu, 2000 (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Wu, Shih-Wei, 2001 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Chen, Albert Chien-Chih, 2001 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Yeh, Yi-Li, 100-00-22005-203.3, 2001 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Liu, Li-Ting, 2000 (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Liu, Rahitzu, 2000 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Tsao, Wen-Chieh, 2000 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Taiwan Fellowship - Pan, Ping-Yu, 1999 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan - Declinations, 2004 June (Box 399, Folder 2)
    - Taiwan - Declinations, 2005 (Box 399, Folder 3)